<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Progress Checker</string>
    <string name="ActionbarTitle">Menu</string>
    <string name="login_email_hint">Email</string>
    <string name="login_password_hint">Password</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login2">LoginActivity2</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="title">Progress Checker</string>
    <string name="Mathvalue1title">What is an equation?</string>
    <string name="Mathvalue1content">When you are solving an equation, you have to move everything except the missing number to one side.
        \nAnything you do to one side, you must also do to the other. For example: 6 + x = 15. To work out the value of x, first subtract 6 from the left side, 6 + x - 6 = x. Then subtract 6 from the right side too, 15 - 6 = 9. So you are left with x = 9.</string>
    <string name="Mathvalue2title">Adding and subtracting fractions</string>
    <string name="Mathvalue2content">It\'s easy to add and subtract fractions when the numbers on the bottom are the same. These are called the denominators.
        \nHowever, sometimes the denominators are different.
        \nYou use equivalent fractions to make them the same.
        \nA common multiple of 2 and 3 is 6. So, for each fraction we need an equivalent fraction with a denominator of 6.
        \nNow you can add these together.</string>
    <string name="Mathvalue3title">Percentages</string>
    <string name="Mathvalue3contnet">The sign % stands for \'per cent\' which means \'out of 100\'.\n\n

40% means 40 out of 100\n\n

11% means 11 out of 100\n\n

To change a percentage to a decimal, divide by 100. Change 48% to a decimal: 48 ÷ 100 = 0.48\n

To change a decimal to a percentage, multiply by 100. Change 0.67 to a percentage: 0.67 x 100 = 67%</string>
    <string name="MathValue4title">What are factors?</string>
    <string name="MathValue4content">Factors are numbers that divide exactly into another number.
        \n \n
For example, the factors of 8 are:
\n
1, 2, 4, 8
\n
Factors can be shown in pairs. Each pair multiplies to make 8.
\n
The factor pairs of 8 can be shown:
\n
1 x 8 = 8
\
2 x 4 = 8</string>

    <string name="ScienceTitle1">Types of energy</string>
    <string name="ScienceContent1">There are two types of energy:
Renewable
Non-Renewable.
        Renewable energy includes solar, hydro and wind energy. Wind energy is made when the wind moves the blades on a wind turbine. This movement creates wind energy which is converted into electrical energy.
        Non-renewable energy includes coal, gas and oil. Most cars, trains and planes use non-renewable energy. They are made by burning fossil fuels to create energy.
    </string>

    <string name="ScienceTitle2">Solids, liquids and gases</string>
    <string name="ScienceContent2"> Solids, liquids and gases are called the three states of matter.
    Solids

    The properties of solids include:

    Solids stay in one place and can be held.
    Solids keep their shape. They do not flow like liquids.
    Solids always take up the same amount of space. They do not spread out like gases.
    Solids can be cut or shaped.
    Even though they can be poured, sugar, salt and flour are all solids. Each particle of salt, for example, keeps the same shape and volume.
    iquids

    The properties of liquids include:

    Liquids can flow or be poured easily. They are not easy to hold.
    Liquids change their shape depending on the container they are in.
    Even when liquids change their shape, they always take up the same amount of space. Their volume stays the same.
    Gases

    The properties of gases include:

    Gases are often invisible.
    Gases do not have a fixed shape. They spread out and change their shape and volume to fill up whatever container they are in.
        Gases can be squashed. </string>

    <string name="ScienceTitle3">What is electricity?</string>
    <string name="ScienceContent3"> Electricity
    Electricity is created by generators which can be powered by gas, coal, oil, wind or solar.

    The electrical energy can be converted into other types of energy such as light, heat, movement or sound.

    Electricity is dangerous, so be careful when using electrical appliances.</string>

    <string name="ScienceTitle4">Solar System</string>
    <string name="ScienceContent4">Solar system facts

    The Sun is a star.
    The Earth is one of eight planets that travel around the Sun.
    The planets are called Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Jupiter, Saturn, Uranus and Neptune.
        The solar system is also home to lots of asteroids, moons, and dwarf planets such as Pluto.</string>

    <string name="ScienceTitle5">What is the Sun?</string>
    <string name="ScienceContent5">Sun facts

    The Sun is a star. It gives out heat and light and makes life possible on Earth.
    The heat and light from the Sun is felt and seen on Earth.
    Stars are orbited by planets.
        The Sun is roughly spherical in shape and is much, much bigger than the Earth. 1,300,000 times bigger!</string>

    <string name="ComputingTitle1">What is an algorithm?</string>
    <string name="ComputingContent1">An algorithm is a set of instructions for solving a problem or accomplishing a task.
Every computerized device uses algorithms, which cut the time required to do things manually.
Algorithmic trading, also known as automated trading or black-box trading, uses a computer program to buy or sell securities at a pace not possible for humans.</string>

    <string name="ComputingTitle2">What is the world wide web?</string>
    <string name="ComputingContent2">The world wide web is a network that connects users aroudn the world to share knwoledge using http/s HyperText Transfer Protocol/Secure.

        Whats the differnece between internet and www?

The internet is a huge network of computers all connected together. The world wide web (‘www’ or ‘web’ for short) is a collection of webpages found on this network of computers. Your web browser uses the internet to access the web.
    </string>

    <string name="ComputingTitle3">How do computers communicate?</string>
    <string name="ComputingContent3">Computer uses binary numbers to communicate with each other. the binary numbers are 0 and 1.

Binary number are calculated by hex to find out the total value. see the example below

binary value = 0000
calculation=    8421

e.g. 1001
cal 8x1,4x0, 2x0,1x1

ans= 8+0+0+1 = 9


</string>

    <string name="ComputingTitle4">What is the ROM?</string>
    <string name="ComputingContent4">ROM is a non-volatile memory which could retain the data even when power is turned off.
The CPU cannot access the data stored on it unless the data is stored in RAM.
The data stored is not as easily accessible as in RAM
Data stored in ROM can only be read.
It stores the instructions required during bootstrap of the computer.
</string>

    <string name="ComputingTitle5">What is the RAM?</string>
    <string name="ComputingContent5">RAM is a volatile memory which could store the data as long as the power is supplied.
The CPU can access the data stored on it.
The data stored is easily accessible
Data stored in RAM can be retrieved and altered.
Used to store the data that has to be currently processed by CPU temporarily.
</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="viewresults">This Graph shows the results of each categories.</string>
    <string name="monitorBehaviour">This Graph shows the interest of the students as they gradually consumes the Study Contents.</string>


</resources>
